本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
翻译
面条打包子处女solo
累不爱
肾功能  肝功能
Kidney function, liver function,
校对
面条打包子
还有睾丸素  我不知道你是怎么搞的
testosterone... I don't know how you did it,
时间轴
薛定谔的猫
但前七个星期里你整整老了四十岁
but you have essentially aged 40 years in the last seven weeks.
时间轴
讷讷
真的吗
Wow. Really?
我们这今早来了个瘾君子
We had a meth addict in here this morning
视效&后期
冰冰爱尖尖
他的生理年龄都比你年轻  他都58岁了
who was biologically younger than you are, and he's 58.
总监
刚solo完的面条打包子
求关怀
[社交网络服务网站]
是个'我的空间'的家伙
MySpace guy.
到底怎么回事
So what is going on?
都是因为那个配置云服务
Uh... It's this cloud service configuration,
我已经在这上面卡了一个多星期了
I've been stuck on it for over a week.
我是个好程序员
I'm a good programmer.
这是我唯一擅长的事
I mean, it's the only thing I am good at.
就去年  我扔飞盘结果敲碎了自己的牙
I mean, last year, I threw a Frisbee and it chipped my tooth.
你要看的可不止是牙医
That's more of a dental issue.
好吧  我
Yup, OK, I...
我要说的是  我17岁时
The point is, I learned
[一个使用Ruby语言写的开源Web应用框架]
用一个周末就掌握了基于Rails平台的Ruby语言
Ruby on Rails over a weekend when I was 17.
我肯定能学会云计算  我必须学会
I should be able to learn cloud, I have to.
你想听听我作为你医生的专业意见吗
Can I give you my professional opinion, as your doctor?
你应该收下盖文·贝尔森那一千万美元
You should have taken that ten million dollars from Gavin Belson,
知道吗
OK?
但你会因后悔而自杀的
But regrets will kill ya
所以千万别太沮丧
so try not to dwell on it.
我之前就提醒过你的
I tried to tell you.
原创翻译  双语字幕
第
一
季
第
六
集
硅
谷
外援  我们才不要什么外援
Outside help? No, we're not getting any outside help.
还有一周就是'科技博客'创业展会
It's a week until TechCrunch,
理查德  不能再等下去了
Richard. We can't wait any longer.
理查德  你看看这块板
Richard, look at the board.
云架构就像是
OK, cloud architecture is
堵住了下水道的一大坨大便
just a giant turd that is clogging up our pipes.
我们得找水管工来疏通下
We have to call in a plumber to fix it.
我讨厌这个比喻  但埃利希说得没错
OK, I hate that metaphor, but Erlich is right.
吉尔弗约尔和我几天前
Gilfoyle and I finished
就把分配服务这块搞定了
the distribution services days ago
我们就一直干坐着等你
and we're just sitting around waiting for you.
我自己能解决
I can solve it.
理查德  你他妈绝对是编程好手
Richard, you're a fucking rock star, OK?
但你就是学不会云计算
You just don't know cloud,
就这么个微不足道的破领域
this tiny, little, shitty area,
现在已经变得举足轻重
which is becoming super important,
在很多方面都称得上是计算机业的未来
and in many ways is the future of computing.
我有点跑题了
That sort of went south on me,
但你明白我的意思
but you understand what I'm saying.
我已经跟彼得·格里高利
I've already talked to
谈过要引入一位顾问
Peter Gregory about insourcing a consultant.
我和一位程序员联系过
I've made contact with a programmer
他在云架构上的造诣
whose cloud architecture
可算得上是登峰造极  人称'雕刻者'
is supposed to be insane. They call him The Carver.
[指恶意破坏网络安全为个人谋利的黑客]
'雕刻者'  那个黑帽黑客
The Carver? That Black Hat guy
黑进了'美国银行'
who apparently hacked into the Bank of America
搞垮了他们整个系统  就那个'雕刻者'
and took down their entire system, that The Carver?
如果可以一定要拉他入伙
We should get him if we can.
好吧  我们可以跟他谈谈
OK, we can talk to the guy,
但他得让我信服才行
but, I mean, he's really gonna have to sell me.
半年前  这帮家伙赚了三千五百万
Six months ago, these guys had 35 million
拿到了新一轮融资
and Series B Financing.
而现在'雕刻者'正在对它进行分拆
Now The Carver's here doing teardown.
他把全部精力都投入到云计算了
He's basically moving their carcass to the cloud.
让世界更美好
什么都不要碰  失败是会传染的
Don't touch anything. Failure is contagious.
应该就是他
I think that's him.
打扰下  雕刻者先生
Excuse me, Mr. Carver?
对  大家都称我为雕刻者
Yeah, uh, people refer to me as The Carver,
但没人当面这样叫我
but no one actually calls me that,
那就是个网名
it's what people call a screen name.
你们懂的
You know.
我叫凯文
I'm Kevin.
好吧  凯文  我们是'魔笛手'的
OK, Kevin, um, we're from Pied Piper,
之前跟你聊过
we spoke earlier.
对  你们这帮人搞砸了  对吧
Yeah, so you guys are fucked, huh?
不  我们才没搞砸
No. No, we're not fucked.
没错  我们简直失败透顶
Yes, we are totally fucked.
我们一星期后要做展示程序
We have a live demo in one week
结果云计算这块便秘了
and our cloud is in the shitter.
-正是如此  -等等  你是理查德
- That's accurate. - Wait, are you Richard?
对  是我
Yes, I am.
你的算法很不错  架构相当完美
Yeah, your algorithm is solid. It's a really good schema.
多谢夸奖
OK, thanks.
你比我想象中老  你多大  25
I did think you'd be younger. What are you, 25?
Twenty-six.
妈呀
Yikes.
我周一时要参加个模拟联合国会议[学术性活动]
Uh, so I have a model U.N. thing on Monday,
但我应该这个周末能把你们的活搞定
but maybe I could burn through your gig over the weekend.
你觉得你能在两天内把活都干完
You think you can do our whole job in two days?
我知道自己两天内能搞定
I know I can do it in two days.
我准备靠美乐耶乐[饮料]
I pound Mello Yello,
[治疗注意力缺失药物  俗称聪明药]
奥利奥和阿德拉过活  做不完我不睡觉
Oreos and Adderall and I don't sleep until I'm done.
好吧
Ok.
但你们知道吗  '基塔翁克'这周末
But you know what? I also have an offer to do some migration
请我去做跨平台移植
at Gittawonk this weekend.
还挺让人兴奋的
It's... it's kind of chill,
而且说实话  他们的技术更强一些
and frankly, their tech's a little stronger.
什么  你说什么
Whoa. What? What?
你觉得'基塔翁克'的技术比我们强
You think Gittawonk's tech is stronger than ours?
真是抱歉  但我可没在PandoDaily[科技网站]上看过
I'm sorry, I don't remember reading in PandoDaily
盖文·贝尔森和彼得·格里高利
that Gavin Belson and Peter Gregory
争抢'基塔翁克'的报道
were fighting over Gittawonk.
从没有人为购买'基塔翁克'开价一千万
No one offered ten million dollars to acquire Gittawonk.
对  我同意理查德说的
Yeah, I agree with Richard,
你应该来为我们工作
you should come work for us.
-什么  -你想要什么  给你咬吗
- What... - What's it gonna take, a blow-job?
因为理查德绝对会吸到你精尽人亡为止
Because Richard will suck the dick right off of your pelvis.
你逗笑我了  狮头男
Now you make me laugh, shaggy man.
好吧  我加入
All right, I'm in.
咱们周五见
I'll see you guys Friday.
好吧
Ok.
-干得好  -是啊
- Well done. - Yeah.
打扰一下  你们好
Excuse me. Hi, um,
你们有兴趣买些糖果吗
would you guys be interested in buying some candy
这样我们教堂才能凑够钱去野营
so you can send my church group to camp?
没兴趣
Nope.
埃利希  拜托
Erlich, come on.
我赌一百块根本没有什么教堂
Hundred bucks says there's no church.
就是骗人的  小人渣
Whole thing's a scam, little scumbags.
他们还只是孩子
They're just children.
看来吉尔弗约尔和他那女撒旦崇拜者
Looks like Gilfoyle and his lady Satanist
从机场回来了
are back from the airport.
你们能想象等下会是什么恶心画面吗
Can you imagine what kind of shit-show this one's gonna be?
[已故英国女歌手]
他说她有种艾米·怀恩豪斯的气场
He says that she has an Amy Winehouse vibe.
那是什么意思
What does that mean?
她也浑身刺青对人生迷失了方向吗
All tatted-up and nowhere to go.
离不开奥施康定[止痛药]的病号吗
Hooked on OxyContin?
也可能是腐烂尸体
Decomposing?
好吧  这也太恶毒了
Oh. Oh, OK, that was dark.
先生们  这位是塔拉
Gentlemen, this is Tara.
-你好  -塔拉  他们是我朋友
- Hi. - Tara, this is the fellas:
贾里德  迪尼希  埃利希和理查德
Jared, Dinesh, Erlich and Richard.
-我是埃利希  -很高兴终于见到你们了
- It's Erlich. - It's great to finally meet you guys.
好了
All right.
老天  他从哪骗来个艾米·怀恩豪斯
Jesus, where did he get Amy Winehouse from?
如果谁能把吉尔弗约尔从她身上扒下来
I mean, I'd have sex with that
我绝对脱了裤子就上
if you hose the Gilfoyle off of her.
家里来了个女的感觉怪怪的
It's weird having a girl in the house.
有种很奇怪的能量
There's a very strange energy.
你好  凯文
Hello... Kevin.
好了  理查德
OK, Richard,
我需要你核准下给凯文的工资
I just need you to approve Kevin's fee.
埃利希已经签过名了  你在这里签名就行
I got Erlich to sign and you sign right there.
两天付他两万美元
Twenty thousand dollars for two days.
你知道还有谁认为我工资太高了吗
You know who else thought my price was too high?
'比特龙'
Bitraptor.
谁
Who?
就是这个意思
Exactly.
好极了  彼得·格里高利马上要出差
Great. Peter Gregory is on his way out of town
我得赶快去找他
so I'm gonna hustle out there
在这个和支票上签字
and get him to co-sign these and the check
我会尽快回来
and I'll be back as soon as I can.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你还好吧  有什么问题吗
You OK over there? You have any questions...?
对  有一个问题
Yeah, one question.
很好  说吧
Cool. Shoot.
为什么你不说话时
Why do you keep your lips
要把嘴闭得那么紧
pressed so tight together when you're not talking?
因为你嘴唇都没血色了
'Cause they're like white.
看起来很不舒服
It looks uncomfortable.
你好  伙计们
Hey, guys.
凯文
Hey, Kevin, um,
你是怎么绕过美国银行的网络安全系统的
so how did you bypass Bank of America's network security?
告诉我点细节
I want details.
我的律师不许我跟别人讨论这个问题
My lawyers told me I'm not allowed to discuss it.
完全理解  就是瞎扯淡
Totally get it. That's baller.
宝贝
Hey, babe?
你醒了
You're up.
好吧  我去洗个澡
All right, I'm gonna go have a shower.
那是怎么回事
Uh, what was that?
怎么了
What?
塔拉跟你说了什么悄悄话
Tara just whispered something to you
之后她看我的眼神就怪怪的
and then she looked at me in a weird way.
不  她才没有
No, she didn't.
她明明就有
Yeah, she did.
怎么回事
What's up?
你知道"同喜"是什么吗
Do you know what compersion is?
就是某些人看到自己所爱之人
It's when someone takes pleasure
被其他人满足时
in seeing their loved one gratified
会感到愉悦
by another person.
特指性满足
Sexually.
与嫉妒正相反
It's the opposite of jealousy.
听起来与正常正相反
It sounds like it's the opposite of normal.
为什么要告诉我这个
Why are you telling me about this thing?
让人震惊的是
As shocking as this is...
塔拉看上你了
...Tara is attracted to you.
你再说一遍
Come again?
是啊  也吓了我一跳  开始的时候
Yeah, freaked me out too, at first.
听你说"开始的时候"有种不祥的预感
I don't like the "At first" part at all.
你到底想说什么
What are you saying?
因为我遵守如下准则
Since I abide by the maxim,
"一切行动随心  这是宇宙法则"
"Do what thou wilt, that is the whole of the law"...
如果你想上我的女朋友  我没有意见
...if you want to fuck my girlfriend, I'm OK with it.
我的老天  伙计
Jesus Christ, man,
你裹着浴巾我都感觉没法靠近你
I could barely stand next to you when you're in your towel.
我可不想跟你们搞3P
I don't want to have a threesome with you.
我不是指3P
I'm not talking about a threesome.
听着  我甚至可以不进屋
Listen, I don't even have to be in the room,
如果那样你更自在的话
unless that's better for you.
好吧  不行  我不能
OK, no, I don't...
好的  那就都解决了
Right, so we're all settled then.
-是的  -你需要停车许可吗
- Yep. - Do you need parking validation?
不用  我用'蹭车'[旧金山地区的一款搭车应用]
No, I used Lyft.
我再蹭车回去就行了
So I'll Lyft it back.
我用彼得的车送你回去吧
Why don't I have Peter's car take you home.
他现在用不着
He's not using it,
我们明天要把车运到艾尔隆去
we're shipping off to Arallon tomorrow.
-艾尔隆  -对  彼得建的那个岛
- Arallon? - Yeah, the island Peter's building.
那条红线是什么
What's the... the red line?
是国际日期变更线
That's the International Date Line.
这座岛正好建在它上面
The island's built right on it
这样西边这半就能在地球上第一个庆祝新年
so the western half can celebrate the first new years on Earth,
第二天  再一起走到东边这半
then the next day, they walk over to the eastern half
来庆祝地球上最后一个新年
and celebrate the last new years on Earth.
但如果能走过去
But if you can walk,
为什么他在岛上还要用车
why does he need the car on the island?
彼得不怎么爱走路
Peter's not really big on walking.
我会让人帮你把车开到门口
So I'll just have the guys pull it up front for you.
好极了
Great.
无人驾驶车辆
Driverless car.
请选择目的地
Select destination.
我要去帕罗奥多市
Hi. Um... I'm going to 5230
加利福尼亚州  帕罗奥多市
纽维尔路5230号
Newell Road, Palo Alto... -
校准行车路线  距目的地距离
Route guidance calibrated. Distance to destination:
4.6英里  请系上安全带
four point six miles. Buckle up, please.
好的
Ok.
请享受这段旅程
Enjoy your ride.
你
You?
塔拉想跟你上床
Tara wants to have sex with you?
你确定
You sure?
对啊  吉尔弗约尔刚刚告诉我的
Yeah, Gilfoyle just told me,
当面说的
to my face.
他说塔拉想跟这屋子里
He told you that Tara wants to copulate with
除了他之外的他人上床
someone else in the house
而这个其他人是你  迪尼希
other than him and that someone is you, Dinesh?
对啊  就是...
Yeah, that's...
你看起来很困惑
You know, you seem confused
但出发点跟我不一样
by this but for a different reason than I am.
你不觉得这很奇怪吗  塔拉想找个陌生人
Don't you think it's weird that Tara wants some strange
结果她选了你没选我
and she chooses you over me,
按理说是人都应该选我
the logical person in the house?
好吧  我知道你的意思了
OK, I see where we are ending up on this.
多谢你陪我
Thank you for your time.
等下  你确定她对吉尔弗约尔说的
Wait, are you sure that she didn't ask Gilfoyle
不是丹麦人  结果你不小心听错了
for a Danish and maybe you misheard her?
也许你是对的  她就是想操一个丹麦人
You're probably right, she just wanted to fuck a Danish.
等下  你就动态生成所有的索引值吗
Wait, you just built all the indexes on the fly?
当然啦
Yeah, of course.
好吧  那这个是什么
OK, well... Well, then what's that?
键值存储
The key-value store.
元组
Tuples.
你听得懂英文吗
Speak English.
你嘴巴又闭得太紧了  伙计
You're kind of doing that lip thing again there, buddy.
不  我才没有
No, I'm not.
别老盯着我嘴巴看
Stop looking at my lips.
目的地重写
新目的地
艾尔隆岛  格里高利区一号
目的地重写  新目的地
Destination override. New destination.
艾尔隆岛  格里高利区一号
One Gregory Drive. Arallon.
距目的地距离  4126英里
Distance to destination: 4,126 miles.
请享受这段旅程
Enjoy your ride.
这是怎么回事
Um, what's happening?
不好意思  怎么...  车先生
I'm sorry, what... Mr. Car?
塔拉和我准备去做撒旦洗礼
Hey. Tara and I are going to a Satanic baptism.
你要一起去吗
You wanna come?
斯图·伯恩斯要与我们一起踏上和魔法之路
Stu Burns decided to walk the Left-Hand path with us.
雅虎的数据库管理员要皈依撒旦
The database administrator for Yahoo is becoming a Satanist?
我们无处不在
We're everywhere.
埃利希  你去吗  迪尼希也去
Hey, Erlich, are you coming? Dinesh is.
他也去
He is?
我是莫妮卡
This is Monica.
莫妮卡  我是贾里德  有个小问题
Hi Monica, it's Jared. Uh, quick question...
贾里德  我现在分不开身
Jared, I can't talk right now.
有个助理把艾尔隆岛工作单上的
One of our assistants has been confusing the eastern,
西部和东部时区全都搞混了
western time zones of Arallon on work orders.
现在很多重大事件都被标到了前一天
Now a bunch of important things are happening a day early.
彼得要是知道了肯定要气死了
Peter is going to be furious when he finds out.
又要发出那种怪声
He's going to make that noise.
糟了  是他打来的  我得挂了
Oh, shit, that's him on the other line, I gotta go.
等下  莫妮卡  我只是
Wait, Monica, I just...
彼得
Hi, Peter.
喂  莫妮卡
Hello, Monica?
车  车先生
Um, car? Mr. Car?
打扰下
Uh, excuse me.
艾尔隆是个岛  那我们怎么
Arallon is an island, so how are we...?
不要  快停下
Oh, no, no! No.
停下  让我出去
Stop. Let me out.
情况不太妙
That's not good.
不要  等下
Oh, no! No!
打扰一下
Excuse me please!
拜托你响下喇叭  拜托叫下吧
Please honk. Please honk.
不要  不要啊啊啊啊啊
No, no, no, no. No, no, no.
不要  求你了  求你们了
No, no. Please. Please.
不好  这可不太妙
Oh, no, that's not good.
好了  唐纳德  保持冷静
OK, Donald, stay calm.
103小时后达到目的地  进入睡眠模式
103 hours to destination. Entering sleep mode.
103小时后达到目的地
进入睡眠模式
-什么  不要  -请享受这段旅程
- What? No! - Enjoy your ride.
好了  保持冷静  要冷静
OK, stay calm. Stay calm.
等下  我的手机
Wait, my phone.
没信号  没信号  没信号  根本没信号
No bars. No bars. No bars. No bars.
宾果游戏
周四  7:15 pm
我们来到您的花园  伟大的路西法
We bring thy garden, o mighty Lucifer,
其中香气满溢  潮气...
the fragrances which abound therein, vapors of...
我们他妈在这里干嘛
What the fuck are we doing here?
你看看这帮神人
Look at these fucking people.
基于此  撒旦的黑色火焰在地狱中熊熊燃烧
...Through this, the black flame of Satan thou walkest in Hell.
地狱之门被冲开
The gates are flung wide
他那守护巨兽绵延不断的嘶吼
and thy passage is heralded by the deathless cries
预示着通往地狱之路
of his guardian beasts.
吸入他的鼻息  夜之兄弟
Breathe of his breath, o brother of the night
滋补他那日益赢弱的大脑
and nourish his waning brain.
在绝望之中
From the despair...
我终于想明白了  这一切都说得通
I just figured it out. It all makes sense.
想明白什么了
Figured what out?
为什么塔拉比起我更喜欢你
Why Tara might be in to you more than me.
她被丑恶所吸引
She's attracted to ugliness.
-去你妈的  -不  你想想看
- Oh, fuck you. - No, think about it.
这就是她选择的生活  对吧
This is the life that she chooses,right?
一无是处对她来说是致命的吸引力
She's attracted to unattractiveness.
你看看这帮丑男
Look at all these ugly people
还有吉尔弗约尔  现在再加上你
and Gilfoyle and now you.
这太扯了  我比你有魅力多了
That's ridiculous. I'm way more attractive than you are.
-不  你才没有  -比你帅多了
- No, you're not. - Way better looking.
从任何角度看
By no metric
你都不可能比我更有魅力
could you possibly be considered more attractive than me.
你是说这世界上所有女人
You're saying that every woman in the entire world
都会觉得你比我更有魅力
would think you're more attractive than I am?
没错  除非她们脑筋都短路了
Yes. Unless they're completely fucked up.
去你的
Damn it.
你还好吧
You doing OK there?
好着呢
Yep, yeah.
挺好的  你知道
Fine, just, you know,
这个编排比较费劲  好多一直在变
it's big orchestration stuff, a lot of moving parts.
你不必操心  就专注于云计算就行了
Nothing you need to worry about. You just focus on the cloud.
如果需要帮忙就叫我
I'm here if you need me.
这么说吧
You know what? Uh...
我知道我们雇你来不是干这个的
I know it's not what we hired you for,
但我在持久层的数据复制上
but I am actually having a little trouble
遇到了点麻烦
with the data replication in the persistence layer.
给我让个地方
Move over.
老天
Oh, Christ.
我比你帅气多了
I'm much more handsome than you are.
才没  我的脸可是完美对称的
No, my face is completely symmetrical.
你知道我小时候的外号吗
You know what my nickname was when I was a kid?
-什么  -巴基斯坦版的丹泽尔[美国影星]
- What? - Pakistani Denzel.
你要是像他就鬼了
You look nothing like him.
丹泽尔·华盛顿的笑超有感染力
Denzel Washington has a beautiful smile.
你这笑简直不能更二
You look ridiculous.
撒旦万岁  仪式结束
Hail Satan, it is done.
-撒旦万岁  -撒旦外岁  仪式
- Hail Satan. - Hail Satan, it is...
结束
...it's done.
谢谢你们前来  各位
Well, thanks for coming, everyone.
杰森兄弟很热心地准备了这周的食物
Brother Jason was kind enough to furnish this week's food.
是炸鸡
It's Chick-fil-A.
我知道基督教右派喜欢吃这个
I know, they're on the Christian right,
但这鸡就是好吃得让人忘了立场
but darned if that chicken isn't good.
我相信黑魔王会理解我们的
I think the Dark Lord would understand.
还有  提醒大家一下
Also... a reminder.
如果你停在了塞万停车场
If you parked in the Sav-On parking lot,
车会被拖走的
they do tow.
我不知道你想要普通的奥利奥还是双倍装
Well, I didn't know if you wanted original Oreos or Double Stuf
我不知道该怎么办  所有两种都卖了
so I went a little nutty and I got both.
怎么样了
How's it, um...
-妈的  妈的  -凯文
- Fuck. Fuck. - Kevin?
人呢
Hello?
妈的
Fuck.
你在桌子底下干嘛呢
What are you doing down here?
我又干了  又干了
I did it again, I did it again.
-干了什么  -我又干了
- Did what? - I did it again.
不好
No.
这是怎么回事
What is this?
你重写了整个数据模式吗
Did you overwrite the data schema?
你为什么要这么做  这种事你想都不该想
Why would you do this? You don't ever do this!
我在美国银行工作时他们也这么说
That's exactly what they said when I was working at BofA.
在美国银行工作  你不是黑进去的吗
Working at BofA? I thought you hacked in.
不是
No.
我当时是对私银行业务部的顾问
I was a consultant at the retail banking services.
我搞垮了他们的整个系统
I crashed their entire system.
最后七个工程师组成的团队花了不止一周
It took a team of seven engineers more than a week
来检查所有代码  以找出我的错误
to comb through all the code and find my mistake.
要想不被起诉
And the only way that I ever avoided being sued
我必须永远不告诉别人我在那工作过
was by agreeing to never tell anyone that I worked there.
妈的
Oh, fuck.
我操  怎么了
Oh, fuck, what?!
我刚刚告诉你了  现在我有麻烦了
I just told you. Now I could get in trouble.
麻烦
Trouble?
你刚刚搞砸了我整个系统
You just skull-fucked my whole system.
你看我不揍你
I am going to punch you in the fucking...
我们可不会用羊来献祭还是别的什么
We don't like sacrifice goats or anything.
我们又不是黄金黎明协会那帮人
We're not like the Order of the Golden Dawners, you know.
是啊
Yeah.
理查德  你还好吧
Richard, are you OK?
迪尼希  我们可能有点小问题
Dinesh, uh, we may have a slight problem.
雕刻者刚刚重塑了我们整个平台
The Carver just carved up our entire platform.
你说什么
What the fuck?
没错  数据库层  应用层
Yeah, the database layers, the application layers,
甚至连chef脚本都重写了
even the chef scripts are fucked.
这个小杂种肯定
The little fucker must have
数据定义语言表
hacked into the DDL tables
就跟他黑'美国银行'时一样
like he did with BofA.
他根本就没黑进'美国银行'
He didn't hack into BofA's.
他当时在那做顾问
He was consulting there at the time,
结果不小心搞糟了整个系统
when he took down the system by accident.
-你还告诉他们了  -搞什么
- Oh, you told them too? - What the fuck?
理查德  你为什么要让这个毛头小子访问数据定义语言表
Richard, why would you let that little fetus access the DDL?
因为我以为这个毛头小子比我强
Because I thought that fetus was better than me
你和大家都这么想
and so did you and everybody
你们就逼着我雇了他
and you just, you pressured me into hiring him...
没错  理查德  但只限于云
Yes, Richard, for the cloud,
让他来调配云配置
to deploy the cloud.
这样你才能有精力做你擅长的
So that you could do what you do best
然后专注于其他事情
and concentrate on everything else
结果全被这小子搞砸了
which the fetus just fucked up.
你得把这个小混蛋
You need to drag this little shit stain...
你听到没
You hear that?
从桌子底下拽出来  让他跟你一起
...Out from under this table and have him go through
检查每一行代码
every single line of code with you
趁还来得及时赶快设法弥补
to unfuck it while it's still unfuckable.
我不该吃那些撒旦鸡块的
I should not have eaten all of that Satanist chicken.
好吧  那这行  你是整个删掉了
OK, and with this one here, did you delete it
还是只是移动它了
or just move it?
醒醒  凯文
Hello? Kevin.
可能吧  我不知道
Maybe. I don't know.
什么  那是什么意思
What? What does that mean?
你有什么毛病  伙计
What's wrong with you, man?
我没法专注  阿德拉吃完了
I can't focus. I'm out of Adderall.
那个贾里德人呢  他该帮我带药回来
Where's that Jared guy? He was getting my refill.
这是个很好的问题
That's actually a really good question.
我不知道他去那了
I don't know where he is.
雕刻者的阿德拉
The Carver's Adderall prescription.
希望不会有什么问题
I hope that's not a problem.
没电了  这是个大问题
Dead battery. That's a problem.
我得去睡会
I need to lay down.
什么  不行
What? No!
你说过你可以连写48小时代码不睡觉
You said you could code for 48 hours straight.
就好像你的超能力一样
That's like your thing.
你以为我是怎么做到的  全靠阿德拉
Yeah, how the fuck do you think I do that? Adderall.
我们这没有
Well, we don't have any.
这里好亮啊
It's really bright in here.
现在谁还吃阿德拉啊
Who takes Adderall anymore?
帕罗奥多一半的孩子
Half the kids in Palo Alto.
你们有没有人有阿德拉
Any of you guys currently on Adderall
而且想赚50美金
and, uh, you know, want to make 50 dollars?
吉尔弗约尔可能藏了摄像头
为吉尔弗约尔而耻
她叫床时会喊"吉尔弗约尔"
吉尔弗约尔的得意脸
做
射精
老天
Oh, boy.
你什么意思  这不是阿德拉
What do you mean, it's not Adderall?
这明明就是
It's Adderall!
我知道阿德拉长什么样  这才不是阿德拉
I know what Adderall looks like. It's not Adderall.
打扰下  凯莱布
Uh, excuse me. Caleb?
这里出了点小差错
There's been some kind of mistake.
你卖给我的不是阿德拉
What you sold me was not actually Adderall.
如果我们可以
So maybe we could...
你觉得你能帮我搞到真正的阿德拉吗
Do you think you could get me some real Adderall?
当然  没问题
Yeah, yeah, of course. Um...
我能办到  或者
I could do that or, um,
让你尝尝这个
I can give you some of this.
我要
OK, I'm gonna...
你要怎么样  贱人
You're gonna do what, bitch?
叫警察抓我吗
Call the cops on me?
告诉他们你从孩子那买来的违法禁药是假的
Tell them you got the wrong illegal drugs from a kid?
你个傻逼  赶快滚蛋
You dumb piece of shit. Get the fuck out of here.
-你  -滚
- Uh, you... - Run!
-好吧  我闪了  -滚远点
- All right, I'm running. - Mm-hm. Keep running!
傻逼
Stupid...
理查德  怎么了
Richard, what's wrong?
你哭了吗
Have you been crying?
是哪一个
Hey! Which one was it?
给了你教堂糖果  对不对
It was church candy, wasn't it?
你这下死定了  小混蛋
You just brought piss to a shit fight, you little cunt!
不  不要
No, no, no!
现在滚回你家  去给我拿五片阿德拉
Now you get in your fucking house and you get me five Adderall
否则我割断你的喉咙  听明白没
or I'll slit your fucking throat! You understand?
我要杀了你妈  鸡奸你爸
I'll kill your mother! I'll rape your father!
我要踩烂你这张小脸
I'll curb-stomp that little face so hard
踩到你牙乱飞才解恨  你个小屁孩
that your teeth will go flying, you little shit!
现在快去  快点
Now go! Go! Go! Go!
马上给我拿五片阿德拉
Get me five Adderall, right now!
好的  我错了  对不起
OK! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
塔拉
Tara.
首先
First of all...
那么
So, um...
我仔细考虑过了
I have thought about it.
想了很多
A lot.
说实话  这整件事的安排
To be honest, elements of this arrangement
还是让我不放心
still trouble me.
但是  我的性经验并不是很丰富
However, I have not had a lot of sexual experiences.
我觉得要是错过这次机会就太傻了
So I feel it may be foolish to turn this down.
所以只要吉尔弗约尔不在屋里
So as long as Gilfoyle is not in the room
能让我检查屋门是否上锁
and I can verify that the door is locked...
我的结论就是
...then I have concluded that...
我愿意
...yes...
我愿意跟你上床
...I would love to have sexual relations with you...
塔拉
...Tara.
我愿意
Yeah.
你在说什么呢
Uh, what are you talking about?
吉尔弗约尔告诉我了
Gilfoyle told me.
我知道你想跟我滚床单
I know you want to have sex with me.
吉尔弗约尔
Gilfoyle?
你能稍微过来下吗
Would you come in here for a second?
你告诉迪尼希我想跟他上床吗
Did you tell Dinesh that I want to have sex with him?
没有
No.
等下  哦对  我说过  都快忘了
Oh, wait, yeah, I totally did. I forgot about that.
我当时嗑了药  就是逗他玩呢
I was really high. I was just fucking with him.
他相信我了
Did he believe me?
你刚刚是来向我女人约炮吗
Did you just present yourself to my woman?
你真是太脱俗了
Oh, this is outstanding.
我的天  你真恶毒
Oh, my God, that is so mean of you!
你看他多可爱
Look at how cute he is.
他超可爱  你很可爱
He's adorable. You're adorable.
别说我可爱  这让我显得很娘炮
Don't call me ador... It's very emasculating.
怎么会有人傻逼到相信吉尔弗约尔的话
What kind of fucking idiot listens to what Gilfoyle has to say?
好了  塔拉  就这么办
OK, Tara, here's what it is.
如果你当着我的面告诉我
If you can tell me to my face
你真的认为迪尼希比我更有魅力
that you seriously find Dinesh more attractive than me,
只有这样我才认输
then and only then will I concede defeat.
怎么了
What?
测试进行中
我们的回归测试  已经完成
And our regression test is... done.
测试进行中
测试通过  搭建完成
好极了  已经完成  全都测试过了
Yes. It's clear, we all test out.
系统又稳定了
The system's stable again.
谢天谢地  现在我们可以进行
Thank God. Now we can move on to
下一个模块  之后我就可以忘记你的存在
the next module and I can forget you ever existed.
你能帮我个忙吗
Can you do me a favor?
别告诉别人是我把系统搞垮了
Don't tell anyone I cratered this bad?
如果你不告诉别人你在这里工作过
I won't tell anyone I hired you
我就不会告诉任何人我雇过你
if you won't tell anyone you worked here.
跟'美国银行'的处理一样
Oh, the BofA deal.
没问题
Got it.
我去给我妈妈打电话  叫她来接我
Well, I'm gonna call my mom and have her pick me up.
你妈妈
Your mom?
顺便说一句  你欠我两万美元
Oh, by the way, you owe me 20 thousand dollars.
真是个混球
What a dick.
这事你得跟贾里德谈
You have to talk to Jared about that.
贾里德人呢
Where is Jared?
打扰下  你能帮帮我吗
Excuse me. Can you help me?
绕过障碍  恢复运行
Obstacle averted. Resuming operations.
请注意安全
Please be careful.
请注意安全  请注意安全
Please be careful. Please be careful.
*我随船远航*
*Sailing takes me away*
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为